Guide to the Edmund Clarence Stedman Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
Edmund Clarence Stedman Papers,
1840-1960.
Stedman, Edmund Clarence, 1833-1908.
120 linear ft. (ca.76,000 items in 87 boxes which include 88 volumes, & 8 oversize items).
Columbia University. Rare Book and Manuscript Library, New York, NY.
MS#1194
4079362
Biographical Note
American poet, anthologist, stockbroker, Civil War journalist.
Scope and Content
Personal and professional papers of Stedman, including correspondence, letter books, diaries, poetry manuscripts, scrapbooks, photographs, and genealogical materials for the Stedman and Dodge families. Correspondence and manuscripts of his mother, Elizabeth Clementine Dodge Stedman Kinney (1810-1889), poet and diarist, and of his granddaughter, Laura Stedman Gould (1881-1941), author and editor. Also, editions of Stedman's LIBRARY OF AMERICAN LITERATURE including printed materials relating to the marketing; and an album of Civil War photographs by Mathew Brady, inscribed by the photographer to Laura H.W. Stedman as well as additional loose photographs by Brady.
1991 addition: Manuscript drafts and notecards for Edward M. Williams' "The Constructive Art", a study of Stedman's literary criticism.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged in 11 series.
Series I: Correspondents, Manuscripts, and Diaries
Series II: Uncataloged Correspondence
Series II: Letterbooks
Series IV: E.C. Stedman’s Writings
Series V: Scrapbooks
Series VI: Financial and Genealogical Material
Series VII: Laura Stedman Gould
Series VIII: Printed Materials
Series IX: Photographs
Series X: Library of American Literature
Series XI: Edward M. Williams
Subjects
American Academy of Arts and Letters.; Keats-Shelley Memorial Association.; National Institute of Arts and Letters (U.S.); Aldrich, Thomas Bailey, 1836-1907.; Bowen, John Eliot, 1858-1890.; Brady, Mathew B., 1823 (ca.)-1896.; Cortissoz, Royal, 1869-1948.; Field, Kate, 1838-1896.; Gould, George M. (George Milbry), 1848-1922.; Gould, Laura Stedman, 1881-1941.; Hearn, Lafcadio, 1850-1904.; Kinney, Elizabeth C. (Elizabeth Clementine), 1810-1889.; Stoddard, Elizabeth, 1823-1902.; Stoddard, Richard Henry, 1825-1903.; Taylor, Bayard, 1825-1878.; Underhill, Edward F. (Edward Fitch), 1830-1898.; Winter, William, 1836-1917.; Woodberry, George Edward, 1855-1930.; United States--History--Civil War, 1861-1865--Personal narratives.; United States--History--Civil War, 1861-1865--Pictorial works.; American literature--19th century.; American poetry--19th century.; Books--Reviews--19th century.; Women authors, American.; Women poets, American.; Albums.; Articles.; Bas-reliefs.; Book reviews.; Card files.; Daguerreotypes.; Diaries.; Drafts (documents).; Engravings.; Essays.; Financial records.; Galley proofs.; Genealogies.; Glass phototransparencies.; Guest registers.; Indexes.; Letter books.; Letterpress copies.; Lists.; Manuscripts.; Memorandums.; Notebooks.; Notes.; Obituaries.; Photographs.; Photoprints.; Poems.; Portraits.; Printing plates.; Proofs.; Reviews.; Scrapbooks.; Speeches.; Authors, American.; Critics; Editors.; Journalists.; Poets, American.; Stockbrokers.; World (New York, N.Y.: 1860-1931)
Access Restrictions
Part of this collection is located off-site. You will need to request this material at least twenty-four (24) hours in advance to use the collection in the Rare Book and Manuscript Library reading room.
Acquisition
1941 M-41 Estate of Laura Stedman Gould Purchase
11/18/1991 M-91-11-18 Manuscripts & card file Williams, E.M. Gift
M-94-07-19 2 letters (Thayer & White) 2293B (Rare Book) Purchase
12/01/1994 M-94-12-01 J.E. Bowen letter 2293B Purchase
05/02/1995 M-95-05-02 2 ms. poems of ECS about Lincoln, in bound vol. 2293B Purchase
08/11/1998 M-98-08-11 1 a.l.s. from ECS to M.W.Stryker 2293B Purchase
Alternate Formats
Elizabeth Kinney volume of personal reminiscences is on microfilm.
Lafcadio Hearn; Lyman W. Case; Royal Cortissoz; Kate Field; William Hamilton Hayne; Edward Howland; Marie Howland; Ellen Mackay and Edward Underhill letters are on microfilm.
- Series I: Correspondence, Manuscripts, and Diaries
  The cataloged correspondence boxes are arranged alphabetically by correspondent and chronologically within that organization. These boxes are located onsite and do not need to be requested ahead of time. When requesting material from this series please make sure to indicate on your call slip that you are requesting boxes from the cataloged portion of the collection.
  - Abbey, Charles T. (Box 1)
  - Abbey, Henry (Box 1)
  - Abernethy, W.E. (Box 1)
  - Adam, Graeme Mercer (Box 1)
  - Adams, Charles Follen (Box 1)
  - Adams, Charles Francis (Box 1)
  - Adams, Charles Josiah (Box 1)
  - Adams, Chester (Box 1)
  - Adams, Ellinor Davenport (Box 1)
  - Adams, George W. (Box 1)
  - Adams, John Quincy, Jr. (Box 1)
  - Adams, Mary Matthews Barnes (Box 1)
  - Adams, Oscar Fay (Box 1)
  - Addey, H. Markinfield (Box 1)
  - Adee, Alvey A. (Box 1)
  - Aikman, Robert (Box 1)
  - Ainsley, Elizabeth Stedman (Box 1)
  - Albany Argus (Box 1)
  - Albee, (Mrs.) Helen R (Box 1)
  - Albee, John, 1884 (Box 1)
  - Albee, John, 1885 (Box 2)
  - Alden, Henry Mills (Box 2)
  - Aldrich, Charles (Box 3)
  - Aldrich, Helen M. (Reeve) (Box 3)
  - Aldrich, Lilian (Woodman) (Box 3)
  - Aldrich, Thomas Bailey (Box 3)
  - Allen, Charles Dexter (Box 3)
  - Allen, Isabella Woodford (Box 3)
  - Allen, James Lane (Box 3)
  - Allen, Marguerite (Box 3)
  - Allen, Willis Boyd (Box 3)
  - Allison, James N. (Box 3)
  - Alvord, Elizabeth Hubbard (Box 3)
  - Armon, John H. (Box 3)
  - Amy, Francis J. (Box 3)
  - Anderson, Ada Woodruff (Mrs.Oliver P.) (Box 4)
  - Anderson, W.H. (Box 4)
  - Andrews, Luch McEntee (Mrs. John N.) (Box 4)
  - Andrews, William S. (Box 4)
  - Angus, W. Craibe (Box 4)
  - Anthony, Andrew V.S. (Box 4)
  - Antrobus, John (Box 4)
  - D. Appleton & Co. (Box 4)
  - Appleton, William Hyde (Box 4)
  - Archbold, Fanny (Box 4)
  - Archer, William (Box 4)
  - Armes, William D (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Andrew Campbell (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Collin (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, F.W. (Box 4)
  - Armstrong, Maitland (Box 4)
  - Arnold, George (Box 4)
  - Arnold, J. Dennis (Box 4)
  - Arnot, M.H. (Box 4)
  - Ashhurst, Richard Lewis (Box 4)
  - Astor, George (Box 4)
  - Atherton, Gertrude (Box 4)
  - Atkinson, Edward (Box 4)
  - Atlantic Monthly (Box 4)
  - Atwell, Marion Gaylord (Box 4)
  - Aubertin, J.J. (Box 4)
  - Auringer, Obadiah Cyrus (Box 4)
  - Austin, Benjamin W. (Box 4)
  - Averill, S. (Box 4)
  - Avery, Samuel Putnam (Box 4)
  - Azeglio, Massimo Tapparelli, Marchese d’ (Box 4)
  - Babcock, William. Henry (Box 5)
  - Bacheller, Irving (Box 5)
  - Bacon, Cleveland F. (Box 5)
  - Bacon, Dolores Marbourg (Box 5)
  - Bacon, Henry (Box 5)
  - Bacon, Theodore (Box 5)
  - Bacon, W.M. (Box 5)
  - Bagby, Albert Morris (Box 5)
  - Bailey, L.C. (Box 5)
  - Bailey, Pearce (for Frederick Peterson) (Box 5)
  - Bainton, George (Box 5)
  - Baird, Henry Carey (Box 5)
  - Baird, Henry Martyn (Box 5)
  - Baker, Christina Hopkinson (Mrs George P.) (Box 5)
  - Baker, Cyrus Osborne (Box 5)
  - Baker, Mrs. L.C. (Box 5)
  - Baker, Margaret (Box 5)
  - Baker & Taylor Co. (Box 5)
  - Baldwin, Henry (Box 5)
  - Baldwin, Lewis (Box 5)
  - Balfour, J.K. (Box 5)
  - Baltzell, Winton J. (Box 5)
  - Bamburgh, William Cushing (Box 5)
  - Bancroft, George (Box 5)
  - Bancroft, Samuel, Jr. (Box 5)
  - Bancroft, William H. (Box 5)
  - Bangs, F.N. (Box 5)
  - Bangs, John Kendrick (Box 5)
  - Bangs, A.F. (Box 5)
  - Bardwell, W.C. (Box 6)
  - Baker, Elsa (Box 6)
  - Baker, John Jesse (Box 6)
  - Barnard, Charles (Box 6)
  - A.S. Barnes & Co. (Box 6)
  - Barnes, Henry B. (Box 6)
  - Barnett, Eugenia (Box 6)
  - Barnum, Charles (Box 6)
  - Baron, John T. (Box 6)
  - Baron, Joseph (Box 6)
  - Barr, Amelia Edith (Box 6)
  - Barrett, F.N. (Box 6)
  - Barrett, William E. (Box 6)
  - Barron, Elwyn Alfred (Box 6)
  - Barrows, Mabel Hay (for Samuel J. Barrows) (Box 6)
  - Barrus, Clara (Box 6)
  - Barry, Charles A. (Box 6)
  - Barry, John D. (Box 6)
  - Barstow, Hollen M. (Box 6)
  - Barstow, Wilson (Box 6)
  - Bartlett, D.W. (Box 6)
  - Bartlett, George A. (Box 6)
  - Bartlett, James (Box 6)
  - Bartlett, Samuel Colcord (Box 6)
  - Bartlett, Washington A (Box 6)
  - Barton, Edmund Mills (Box 6)
  - Barton, Frederick (Box 6)
  - Barton, Samuel (Box 6)
  - Bashford, Herbert (Box 6)
  - Bates, Alfred Elliott (Box 6)
  - Bates, Arlo (Box 6)
  - Bates, Charles A. (Box 6)
  - Bates, Edward (Box 6)
  - Bates, Herbert (Box 6)
  - Bates, Katharine Lee (Box 6)
  - Bates, Mrs. Marget Holmes (Ernsperger) (Box 6)
  - Baxter, E.R., & Co. (Box 6)
  - Baxter, James Phinney (Box 6)
  - Baylor, Frances Courtenay (Box 6)
  - Baym, William (Box 6)
  - Beard, W.L.G. (Box 7)
  - Beckwith, Carroll (Box 7)
  - Beebe, Walton (Box 7)
  - Beers, C. Eliot (Box 7)
  - Beers, Henry A. (Box 7)
  - Behenna, K.A. (Box 7)
  - Belden, Mrs. Jessie Van Zile (Box 7)
  - Belford, Clarke & Co. (Box 7)
  - Bell, Clark (Box 7)
  - Bell, (Henry Thomas) Mackenzie (Box 7)
  - Bell, Nicholas J .A. (Box 7)
  - Bell, Ralcy Husted (Box 7)
  - Bell, Robert Mowry (Box 7)
  - Bellah, Lillian (Box 7)
  - Bellamy, Elizabeth Whitfield Groom (Box 7)
  - Bellamy, Francis (Box 7)
  - Bellows, [Albert Fitch] (Box 7)
  - Bellows, M. Fannie (Box 7)
  - Benedict, Clara Woolson (Box 7)
  - Benedict, Frank Lee (Box 7)
  - Benedict, George (Box 7)
  - Benham, Alida G.K. (Box 7)
  - Benjamin, Marcus (Box 7)
  - Benjamin, Park (Box 7)
  - Benjamin, Samuel Greene Wheeler (Box 7)
  - Benjamin. William Evarts (Box 7)
  - Bennett, Henry Holcomb (Box 7)
  - Bennett, Henry Silliman (Box 7)
  - Bennett, John (Box 7)
  - Bennetto, John (Box 7)
  - Bensel, James Berry (Box 7)
  - Benson, Arthur Christopher (Box 7)
  - Benson,.Clarence S. (Box 7)
  - Benson,. Louis·Fitzgerald (Box 7)
  - Benson, Joel (Box 7)
  - Berger, Will F (Box 7)
  - Berry, M.D. (Box 7)
  - Bertram, James (Box 7)
  - Betts, Craven Langstroth (Box 7)
  - Bevin, S. Marie (Box 7)
  - Bianchi, Martha Gilbert (Dickinson) (Box 8)
  - Bierce, Ambrose (Box 8)
  - Bierstadt, Albert (Box 8)
  - Bierstadt, Rosalie H. Osborne Ludlow (Mrs. Albert) (Box 8)
  - Bigelow, John (Box 9)
  - Bigelow, Lucius (Box 9)
  - Bigelow, Poultney (Box 9)
  - Bigelow, W.S. (Box 9)
  - Billings, Edward C. (Box 10)
  - Billings, John Shaw (Box 10)
  - Birckhead, William Hunter (Box 10)
  - Bird, Frederic Mayer (Box 10)
  - Birkmaier, Elizabeth G. (Mrs. George L.) (Box 10)
  - Bishop, George R. (Box 10)
  - Bishop, Mary Catherine (Box 10)
  - Bishop, Joseph Bucklin (Box 10)
  - Bishop, Pauline (Box 10)
  - Bishop, William Henry (Box 10)
  - Bispham, David Scull (Box 10)
  - Bispham., William (Box 10)
  - Bjerregaard, Carl Henrick Andreas (Box 10)
  - Black, Alexander (Box 10)
  - Black, Henry V.D. (Box 10)
  - Black, John W. (Box 10)
  - Blackwell, Antoinette Brown (Box 10)
  - Blacque, V.A. (Box 10)
  - Bladen, Elizabeth S. (Box 10)
  - Blagden, Isa Jane (Box 10)
  - Blair, W.A (Box 10)
  - Blake, Isabel (Box 10)
  - Bladen, Charles Granger (Box 10)
  - Blanine, Joseph L. (Box 10)
  - Blatchford, Pattye L. (Box 10)
  - Blauvelt, William H. (Box 10)
  - Bliss, Cornelius Newton (Box 10)
  - Bliss, H.L. (Box 10)
  - Block, Louis J. (Box 10)
  - Bloede, Gertrude (Box 10)
  - Blood, Henry Ames (Box 10)
  - Bloor, Alfred Janson (Box 10)
  - Blouet, Marie (Mrs. Leon Paul) (Box 10)
  - Blouet, Leon Paul (Box 10)
  - Blumenschein, Ernest L. (Box 10)
  - Boardman, Samuel (Box 11)
  - Bok, Edward W (Box 11)
  - Bok, William J. (Box 11)
  - Boker, George H. (Box 11)
  - Bolles, Frank (Box 11)
  - Bolton, Sarah. Knowles (Box 11)
  - Boltwood, Henry L. (Box 11)
  - Bond, Frank (Box 11)
  - Bond, Henry R (Box 11)
  - Boner, John Henry (Box 11)
  - Boone, Sallie (Box 12)
  - Booth, Mary Louise (Box 12)
  - Bostwick., Arthur E (Box 12)
  - Bota, Anne Charlotte Lynch (Box 12)
  - Boult, Ella. M (Box 12)
  - Bowen, Clarence W. (Box 12)
  - Bowen, Henry C. (Box 12)
  - Bowen, Herbert Wolcott (Box 12)
  - Bowen, John Eliot (Box 12)
  - Bowker, Richard Rogers (Box 12)
  - Bowles, Samuel (Box 12)
  - Boyd, Louis (Box 12)
  - Boyesen, Elizabeth Keen (Mrs. Hjalmar H.) (Box 12)
  - Boyesen, Hjalmar H. (Box 12)
  - Boyesen, Hjalmar Hjorth, Jr. (Box 12)
  - Boynton, Louise (Box 12)
  - Brackett, Anna Callender (Box 13)
  - Bradley, Mary Emily Neely (Box 13)
  - Braeme, Mary Gray (Box 13)
  - Brainard, Mary G. (Box 13)
  - Brainerd, Cephas (Box 13)
  - Brainerd, James H (Box 13)
  - Braithwaite, William Stanley (Box 13)
  - Branch, Anna Hampstead (Box 13)
  - Brankang, Curt (Box 13)
  - Branllyee, A. (Box 13)
  - Brenner, E.J. (Box 13)
  - Brett, George E. (Box 13)
  - Brett, George P. (Box 13)
  - Bridges, A.F. (Box 13)
  - Bridges, Robert (Box 13)
  - Briggs, William (Box 13)
  - Bristed, [Charles Astor] (Box 13)
  - Bristol, Charles L. (Box 13)
  - Brock, Robert Alonzo (Box 14)
  - Bromley, Isaac (Box 14)
  - Brooke, E.S. (Box 14)
  - Brooke, Stopford Augustus (Box 14)
  - Brooke, Henry M. (Box 14)
  - Brooks, Henry S. (Box 14)
  - Brooks, Noah (Box 14)
  - Brooks, Phillips (Box 14)
  - Brotherton, Alice Williams (Box 14)
  - Brown, Colin Rae (Box 14)
  - Brown, Demetra Vaka (Mrs Kenneth) (Box 14)
  - Brown, Frederick (Box 14)
  - Brown, Kenneth (Box 14)
  - Brown, Minnie C. (Box 14)
  - Brown, Theron (Box 14)
  - Brown, W. E. (Box 14)
  - Browne, A.G., Jr. (Box 14)
  - Browne, Francis Fisher (Box 14)
  - Browne, [Frank] G. (Box 14)
  - Browne, Irving (Box 14)
  - Brown,. Junius Henri (Box 14)
  - Browne, Minnie R (Box 14)
  - Browne, Rufus Key (Box 14)
  - Brownell, Atherton (Box 14)
  - Brownell, [William Crary] (Box 14)
  - Brownson, Earl Leo (Box 14)
  - Bruce, Wallace (Box 14)
  - Brunton, Th. (Box 14)
  - Bryce, Lloyd (Box 14)
  - Buck, Dudley (Box 15)
  - Buck, Gertrude (Box 15)
  - Buck, Richard Henry (Box 15)
  - Buckham, James (Box 15)
  - Buckley, James Monroe (Box 15)
  - Bucklin, William Savery (Box 15)
  - Buel, Clarence Clough (Box 15)
  - Buffington, E. D. (Box 15)
  - Bulkley, C.H.A. (Box 15)
  - Bull, Julia P. (Mrs. John C.) (Box 15)
  - Billard, Laura Curtis (Box 15)
  - Bult, Henry B (Box 15)
  - Bunce, Oliver Bell (Box 15)
  - Bunner, Henry Cuyler (Box 15)
  - Burbank, Alfred Post (Box 15)
  - Burbank, E.M.B. (Box 15)
  - Burleigh, George Shepard (Box 15)
  - Burlingame, Edward Livermore (Box 15)
  - Burnett, Charles H. (Box 15)
  - Burnstine, Isadore (Box 15)
  - Buronzo, (Comte) Boniface de (Box 15)
  - Burpee, Lawrence J. (Box 15)
  - Burr, L. (Box 15)
  - Burritt, Marion Tilden (Box 15)
  - Burroughs, John (Box 15)
  - Burt, A.W. (Box 15)
  - Burt, Mary Elizabeth (Box 15)
  - Burton, Rachel C. (Box 15)
  - Burton, Richard (Box 15)
  - Bushnell, Frances Louisa (Box 15)
  - Butler, George Bernard (Box 15)
  - Butler, Nicholas Murray (Box 15)
  - Butler, Prescott Hall (Box 15)
  - Butler, William Mill (Box 15)
  - Butter, Blanche M. (Box 15)
  - Butterworth, Hezekiah (Box 15)
  - Butts, Mary Frances (Box 15)
  - Buxton, Francis (Box 15)
  - Byars, William Vincent (Box 16)
  - Byington, A Homer (Box 16)
  - Bynner, Edwin Lassetter (Box 16)
  - Bynner, Hall Witter (Box 16)
  - Byrne, Thomas (Box 16)
  - Byron, Mrs. May C. (Gillington) (Box 16)
  - Cable, George Washington (Box 16)
  - Cahill, Frank (Box 16)
  - Calder, Ellen M. (Box 16)
  - Caldwell, L.H. (Box 16)
  - Calhoun, Martha (Box 16)
  - Cameron, A. (Box 16)
  - Cameron, Simon (Box 16)
  - Camm, L.G.B. (?) (Box 16)
  - Campbell, Charles B. (Box 16)
  - Campbell, [William Wilfred] (Box 16)
  - Canfie1d, James Hulme (Box 16)
  - Carey, Frederick (Box 16)
  - Carey, William (Box 16)
  - Carleton, George Washington (Box 16)
  - Carleton, Henry Guy (Box 16)
  - Carleton, Will (Box 16)
  - Carling, James (Box 16)
  - Carlisle, Annie A. Stedman (Box 16)
  - Carman, Bliss (Box 16)
  - Carnegie, Andrew (Box 16)
  - Carpenter, Amelia Walstein Jolls (Box 17)
  - Carpenter, Esther Bernon (Box 17)
  - Carpenter, George Rice (Box 17)
  - Carpenter, Henry Bernard (Box 17)
  - Carpenter, Horace Thompson (Box 17)
  - Carpenter, John C. (Box 17)
  - Carpenter, William Henry (Box 17)
  - Carrington, John B. (Box 17)
  - Carryl, Charles Edward (Box 17)
  - Carryl, Guy Wetmore (Box 17)
  - Carus, Paul. (Box 17)
  - Cary, Alice (Box 17)
  - Cary, Edward (Box 17)
  - Case, E.W. (Mrs. Lyman C. Case) (Box 17)
  - Case, Lyman (Box 17)
  - Case, Mark (Box 17)
  - Catherwood, Mary Hartwell (Box 17)
  - Cawein, Madison J. (Box 17)
  - Cesnola, Luigi Palma di (Box 17)
  - Chace, Jonathan (Box 18)
  - Chadbourne, William R. (Box 18)
  - Chadwick, John White (Box 18)
  - Chamberlin, Emerson (Box 18)
  - Chamberlin, W.U. (Box 18)
  - Chambers, George W. (Box 18)
  - Chambers, Julius (Box 18)
  - Chambers, Robert W. (Box 18)
  - Chambers, William P. (Box 18)
  - Champlin, George G. (Box 18)
  - Champlin, John Denison (Box 18)
  - Champney, Elizabeth Williams (Box 18)
  - Champney, James Wells (Box 18)
  - Chandler, Charles Edward (Box 18)
  - Channing, William F. (Box 18)
  - Channing-Stetson, Grace Ellery (Box 18)
  - Chanute, Octava (Box 18)
  - Chapman, John Jay (Box 18)
  - Charles, Emily Thornton (Box 18)
  - Chase, Clement (Box 18)
  - Chase, S.B. (Box 18)
  - Chatfield., E.H. (Box 18)
  - Chatto, Andrew (Box 18)
  - Cheney, E.C. (Box 18)
  - Cheney, John Vance (Box 18)
  - Cheney, Warren (Box 18)
  - Chew, Beverly (Box 18)
  - Child, Frank Samuel (Box 18)
  - Childs, Eleanor Stuart (Box 18)
  - Chilton, Carroll Brent (Box 18)
  - Chittenden, William. Laurence (Box 18)
  - Choate, Joseph Hodges (Box 18)
  - Christie, Samuel A (Box 18)
  - Christopher, Marion (Box 18)
  - Church, Francis Pharcellus (Box 18)
  - Church, Mary Elizabeth Metcalf (Mrs William) (Box 18)
  - Church, Willard (Box 18)
  - Church, William. Conant (Box 18)
  - Ciat, Louis Jacob (Box 19)
  - Clacknell, John Edmund Richard (Box 19)
  - Clapp, Alexander H. (Box 19)
  - Clapp, Henry (Box 19)
  - Clark, Charles Hopkins (Box 19)
  - Clark, George Edward (Box 19)
  - Clark, Henry R (Box 19)
  - Clark, Henry H (Box 19)
  - Clark, James Gowdy (Box 19)
  - Clark, John A (Box 19)
  - Clark, Kate Upson (Box 19)
  - Clark, Mary Vida (Box 19)
  - Clark, Thomas P. (Box 19)
  - Clark, Willis Gaylord (Box 19)
  - Clarke, Charles E (Box 19)
  - Clarke, Helen Archibald (Box 19)
  - Clarke, Isaac Edwards (Box 19)
  - Clark, Joseph Ignatius Constantine (Box 19)
  - Clarke, Robert & Co. (Box 19)
  - Clarke, T.M. (Box 19)
  - Clarke, W.T. (Box 19)
  - Clarke, William Fayal (Box 19)
  - Clarkson, Helen Howell (Box 19)
  - Clearwater, Alphonso Trumpbour (Box 20)
  - Clemens, Samuel Langhorne (Box 20)
  - Clement, Edward Henry (Box 20)
  - Clement, W.K. (Box 20)
  - Clemdenin, Frank Montrose (Box 20)
  - Cleveland, Charles (Box 20)
  - Cleveland, Clement (Box 20)
  - Cleveland Edmund James (Box 20)
  - Cleveland, Frances Folsom (Mrs. Grover) (Box 20)
  - Cleveland, Horace William Shaler (Box 20)
  - Cleveland, James Butler (Box 20)
  - Cleveland, Lucy (Box 20)
  - Cleveland, Marguerite (Box 20)
  - Cleveland, Rose Elizabeth (Box 20)
  - Clifton, F (Box 20)
  - Cloud, Virginia. Woodward (Box 20)
  - Clymer, Ella Dietz (Box 20)
  - Clymer, Meredith (Box 20)
  - Clymer,·W.B.S. (Box 20)
  - Coan, Titus Munson (Box 20)
  - Coates, Edward H. (Box 21)
  - Coates, Florence Earle (Box 21)
  - Coates, Henry Troth (Box 21)
  - Cobb, James T. (Box 21)
  - Cochran, Michael (Box 21)
  - Cocke, William Archer (Box 21)
  - Cocke, Zitella (Box 21)
  - Cockerill, John Albert (Box 21)
  - Coffey, Titian J. (Box 22)
  - Coffin, Charles Carleton (Box 22)
  - Cohn, Louis H (Box 22)
  - Colby, Bainbridge (Box 22)
  - Cole, Colonel Ashley W. (Box 22)
  - Coleman, Grace Hallam (Box 22)
  - Coleman, Harry (Box 22)
  - Coleman, Sarah D (Box 22)
  - Coleman, Vernetta E. (Box 22)
  - Coles, Abraham (Box 22)
  - Coles, Emilie S. (Box 22)
  - Coles, Jonathan Ackerman (Box 22)
  - Collier, Peter Fenelon (Box 22)
  - Collier, Thomas Stephens (Box 22)
  - Collins, Charles (Box 22)
  - Collins, Edmund (Box 22)
  - Collins, Laura Sedgwick (Box 22)
  - Collyer, Robert (Box 22)
  - Colton, Arthur Willis (Box 22)
  - Colton, Gardner Quincy (Box 22)
  - Comstock, Warren E. (Box 22)
  - Conant, C.B. (Box 22)
  - Conant, Helen Charlotte Stevens (Box 22)
  - Conant, S.S. (Box 22)
  - Condon, Randall Judson (Box 22)
  - Cone, Helen Gray (Box 22)
  - Cones, Jean Augusta (Box 22)
  - Congdon, Charles Taber (Box 22)
  - Conkling, Alfred Ronald (Box 22)
  - Connor, John F. (Box 22)
  - Converse, George S. (Box 22)
  - Conway, Ellen Dana (Mrs. Moncure D) (Box 22)
  - Conway, Eustace (Box 22)
  - Conway, Katherine Eleanor (Box 22)
  - Conway, Moncure (Box 22)
  - Conwell, M.C. (Box 22)
  - Cook, Albert Stanburrough
  - Cook, Clarence
  - Cook, J.M.
  - Cook, Louisa W. de Windt
  - Cooke, George Willis
  - Cooke, Rollin H.
  - Coolbrith, Ina Donna
  - Coombes, George J.
  - Coombs, Anne Sheldon
  - Cooper and Graff
  - Corey, Susan Pratt Dodge (Mrs Uzal)
  - Cornwallis, Kinaham
  - Corrigan, Margaret Stone
  - Cortizzo, Royal
  - Cortland, Gertrude Whittier
  - Coster, Robert
  - Cotterell, George
  - Cotton, James Sutherland
  - Cottrell, Mary & Sophia Augusta
  - Cowen, Philip
  - Cowles, Alfred Abernethy
  - Cowles, Eugene
  - A.J. Cox & Co.
  - Cox, Samuel Sullivan
  - Coxe, Arthur Cleveland
  - Coxe, Macgrane
  - Coxe, Reginald Cleveland
  - Coxe, Virginia Rosalie
  - Coyle, Henry
  - Craigie, Jeanine L. (Box 24)
  - Crandall, Charles Henry (Box 24)
  - Crane, Elizabeth Green (Box 24)
  - Crane, Warren C. (Box 24)
  - Crawford, Tarlstoh Perry (Box 24)
  - Crim, Matt (Box 24)
  - Crissey, Forest (Box 24)
  - Croffut, William Augustus (Box 24)
  - Croly, David Goodman (Box 24)
  - Croly, Jennie C (Box 24)
  - Crosby, A.B. (Box 24)
  - Crosby, Ernest Howard (Box 24)
  - Crosby, Mary L. Pierpont (Box 24)
  - Crouch, Frederick Nicholls (Box 24)
  - Crouch, George (Box 24)
  - Crowinshield, Arent Schuyler (Box 24)
  - Cubin, John (Box 24)
  - Culberson, Charles Allen (Box 24)
  - Cummins, Mrs. Adley H. (Box 24)
  - Cunliffe-Owen, J. (Box 24)
  - Currier, Andrew F (Box 24)
  - Curtis, Anna Shaw (Mrs. George W.) (Box 24)
  - Curtis, George William (Box 24)
  - Custer, Elizabeth Bacon (Mrs. George A.) (Box 24)
  - Cutter, Ephraim (Box 24)
  - Cutter, J.E. (Box 24)
  - Cuyler, Theodore L (Box 24)
  - Daggett, Rollin Mallory (Box 24)
  - Daingerfield, Elliot (Sec., The Emma Lazarus Memorial Committee) (Box 24)
  - Dale, L.M. (Box 24)
  - Damrosch, Margaret Blaine (Box 24)
  - Dana, Carrie M. (Box 25)
  - Dana, Elizabeth Ellery (Box 25)
  - Dana, Francis (Box 25)
  - Dandridge, Danske (Box 25)
  - Dangerfield, James, .Jr. (Box 25)
  - Daniel, Thomas (Box 25)
  - Daniels, George H. (Box 25)
  - Daniels, J.H. (Box 25)
  - D'Arcy, Ella (Box 25)
  - Dargan, Olive Tilford (Mrs. Pegram) (Box 25)
  - Davidson, Robert (Box 25)
  - Davidson, W.T. (Box 25)
  - Davies, John W., & Con. (Box 25)
  - Davis, Eleanor B. (Box 25)
  - Davis, James (Box 25)
  - Davis, Mary Evelyn (Moore) (Box 25)
  - Davis, Noah (Box 25)
  - Davis, Richard Harding (Box 25)
  - Davis, William T. (Box 25)
  - Dawson, J. (Box 25)
  - Dawson, Thomas F. (Box 25)
  - Day, Richard Edwin (Box 25)
  - Day, Thomas Fleming (Box 25)
  - Dazey, Charles Turner (Box 25)
  - Deane, .Joseph G. (Box 25)
  - De Cordova, Alfred (Box 25)
  - De Forest, John William (Box 25)
  - De Grove, Ritzema (Box 25)
  - DeHaven, .A.H. (Box 25)
  - de Kahn, Carolina. J. (Box 25)
  - De Kay, Charles (Box 25)
  - De Kay, Drake (Box 25)
  - de Lagutry, Norman (Box 25)
  - Deland, Margaret (Box 25)
  - Dellenballgh, Frederick, Samuel (Box 25)
  - De Luce, Percival (Box 25)
  - Demarest, Emma (Box 25)
  - Deming, Philander (Box 25)
  - Dennen, Grace Atherton: (Box 25)
  - Dennett, William S. (Box 25)
  - Derby, Frank H. (Box 26)
  - Derby, James Cephas (Box 26)
  - De Vere, Cecelia (Box 26)
  - De Vere, Mary Aigne (Box 26)